cityblis.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy | Cityblis

### You have no item history

#### We will save the latest products you viewed here for you

### Loading...

### You have no "blised" items

#### We will save everything you have "Liked" here for you

### Loading...

## By invitation only

### For our invited designer members

* * *

#### Are you a Unique Designer?

Cityblis is an invitation only community for unique designers and artists. Membership in Cityblis allows you access to a host of exclusive benefits and privileges.

#### Your designs showcased to the world

As an exclusive member of Cityblis, designers receive invitations to fashion events, trade shows and access to international buyers and procurement houses. Through our partners we are able to publish stories across social networks and fashion magazines around the world.

There are no costs, commissions or fees involved in joining Cityblis. Designers are only allowed to join Cityblis by invitation or recommendation. Before granting membership access, every new designer is screened to ensure Cityblis quality standards.

To request exclusive membership, submit your website or look book to:

We look forward to hear from you and sharing your brand with fashion lovers everywhere.

Sincerely  
_**Amanda Davis**_  
Head of Cityblis Community

Our privacy policy sets out how we will use your information. Company will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of anonymized customer research and profiling, to suggest stores and items on CityBlis based on your actions and the actions of other users on the site, or where we have your express permission to do so. We will not sell your personally identifiable information (name, address, e-mail address or credit card information) to any third party (excluding partners from whom you may have linked to our site) without your permission.

Personally identifiable information comprises any information that can help us identify or locate an individual, including, without limitation, an individual’s name, address, e-mail address. 

Non-personally identifiable information comprises information that does not by itself identify an individual. This information generally includes anonymous information about an individual’s browsing habits that includes, among other things, the websites visited, information concerning date and time of visit, IP address, the type of browser and operating system used. 

When you log-in to CityBlis your profile may display your picture, e-mail address and phone number. You may choose not to display these by editing your profile. If you choose to make personally identifiable information public then Company is under no obligation to protect it. Any comments you make or reviews you post will be viewable on your profile. If you wish for these comments to no longer be public you must delete the comments. 

## 1.1 COMMUNICATION & MARKETING

If you have made a purchase from a CityBlis store we may occasionally update you on the latest products, news and special offers via e-mail. You will also be given the opportunity to receive such communications from us and selected third parties when you join CityBlis. 

All CityBlis members have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us and/or selected third parties you should opt-out by visiting 'Your Details' in 'Your Account' on the CityBlis website. You can access 'Your Account' once you register and login. Or click on the "unsubscribe" link in any email communications. 

## 1.2 COOKIES 

A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. If you have registered with us then your computer will store an identifying cookie which will save you time each time you re-visit CityBlis, by remembering your email address for you. You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer without your explicit consent. 

## 1.3 SITE STATISTICS

We may disclose aggregate, anonymous statistics about the number of visitors to CityBlis or number of purchases made as required by our investors or advertisers or potential sellers. We may use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to CityBlis on our behalf using cookies and code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. CityBlis uses and stores this type of information, to help it improve the services to its users. 

### 1.3.1 Protecting your security

We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity - a credit check is not performed and your credit rating is unaffected. 

### 1.3.2 Transfers of your Information

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for Company or one of our suppliers. Such processing may, for example, be required in order to fulfill your order, process your payment details or provide support services. 

The transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

## 1.4 DISCLOSURES OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties: 

• if CityBlis or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets; or 

• if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Service/User Agreement and Policies, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of CityBlis, Company, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

## 1.5 THIRD PARTY SITES

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

## 1.6 CHECKING YOUR DETAILS

If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to CityBlis you may do so by contacting us via the e-mail address or address given in our Terms of Service/User Agreement. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.
